{
    "subject": "resource/Laza_Ristovski",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Serbian_rock_keyboardists",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Laza Ristovski's work is Category:Serbian rock keyboardists.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8146024346351624,
            "question": "What is the impact of Laza Ristovski's music on Serbian rock?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6685200929641724,
            "question": "Is Laza Ristovski considered a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6429415345191956,
            "question": "Can you name any Serbian rock bands Laza Ristovski has been a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5555291175842285,
            "question": "What genre of music is Laza Ristovski known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5018205642700195,
            "question": "What musical period or era is Laza Ristovski associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4992676377296448,
            "question": "What instrument does Laza Ristovski primarily play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4517134428024292,
            "question": "What nationality is Laza Ristovski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44325077533721924,
            "question": "Has Laza Ristovski received any awards or recognition for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4017340838909149,
            "question": "Are there any other musicians Laza Ristovski has collaborated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30705752968788147,
            "question": "Are there any notable songs or albums by Laza Ristovski?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Laza Ristovski's work is Category:Serbian rock keyboardists.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1053_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other musicians Laza Ristovski has collaborated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1053_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Laza Ristovski received any awards or recognition for his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1053_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Laza Ristovski?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1053_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1053_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the documents, Laza Ristovski was a keyboard player for notable Yugoslavian rock bands, such as Smak and Bijelo Dugme, and his solo work is categorized as electronic music with characteristics of prog and new age styles, which aligns with Category:Serbian rock keyboardists."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Laza Ristovski, mentioning his involvement in Yugoslav and Serbian music scenes as a keyboardist. This supports the statement that he is categorized under \"Category:Serbian rock keyboardists.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}